Guide to the George P. Hall & Son Photograph Collection [1876-1914] PR 24
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series IV: Photographs by Subject
  - Portraits - Unmounted
    - Fire Co. 57 in front of Victoria Station, undated (Box 26, Folder 235)
    - Hall, James S., studio portrait, undated (Box 26, Folder 235)
    - Hall, James S., with a group of unidentified friends (2), undated (Box 26, Folder 235)
    - Hall, George P., family portrait at residence, undated (Box 26, Folder 235)
    - Hope Fishing Club on steps of unidentified building, 1911 (Box 26, Folder 235)
    - Johnson, Rev. Samuel (1696-1772), President of King's College [photograph of painting], undated (Box 26, Folder 235)
    - Lawrence, L.W., seated at desk, interior, undated (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - Manhattan Beach Hotel Guests in front of Hotel, undated (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - Masonic Club, group portrait, undated (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - Men's Club, group portrait in front of building entrance, undated (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - Morgan, J.P. [copy photographs](2), undated (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - Nostrand family, at Shelter Island, undated (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - St. Paul's School, Concord, N.H., Mandolin Club, [1900] (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - Sullivan, John L. with Yank Sullivan, Yank Sullivan, Jr., Tom O'Brien, and Jack Barnitt, interior [signed "Your Friend, John L. Sullivan"], undated (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - Tansley Republican Club, interiors (2), undated (Box 26, Folder 236)
    - Unidentified (8), [1900], undated (Box 26, Folder 237)
  - Portraits - Mounted
    - Church congregation, in front of unidentified 1860 church, [1876] (Box 26, Folder 238)
    - Graduation ceremony, children in interior of hall, [1908-1912] (Box 26, Folder 238)
    - Hall, Leila (Mrs. James S.) (3 copies), undated (Box 26, Folder 239)
    - Lipton, Sir Thomas, in group portrait, undated (Box 26, Folder 240)
    - St. Paul's Churchyard, cadets at entrance, undated (Box 26, Folder 240)
    - Unidentified group of boys and men in uniform on street (2), undated (Box 26, Folder 241)
    - Unidentified man in automobile, undated (Box 26, Folder 241)
  - Ships - Unmounted
    - Chester W. Chapin, undated (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - Favorite, undated (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - U.S.S. Georgia, undated (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - Grant, U.S. Army Transport, New York City in background, 1899 (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - Hooker, U.S. Army Transport, in New York Harbor, 1899 (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - U.S.S. Indiana, 1898 (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - Keying, Chinese Junk [Photograph of Currier & Ives lithograph, 1847], undated (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - U.S.S. Miantonomah, 1898 (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - U.S.S. New Jersey, undated (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - U.S.S. New York, undated (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - New Yorker, fire boat, undated (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - U.S.S. Oregon, 1898 (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - U.S.S. Texas, 1898 (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - U.S.S. Vixen (2 copies), 1898 (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - City of Worcester, steamboat of the N.Y. Excursion Co., undated (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - Zephyr, steamboat of the N.Y. Excursion Co., undated (Box 26, Folder 243)
  - Ships - Mounted
    - Alabama, undated (Box 27, Folder 244)
    - R.M.S. Baltic, undated (Box 27, Folder 244)
    - John A. Bouker, tugboat, with crew, undated (Box 27, Folder 244)
    - U.S.S. Brooklyn, 1898 (Box 27, Folder 245)
    - Buford, U.S. Army Transport, undated (Box 27, Folder 245)
    - Burnside, U.S. Army Transport, [1900] (Box 27, Folder 245)
    - Chicago, undated (Box 27, Folder 246)
    - Comus, in Hudson River, [1900] (Box 27, Folder 246)
    - Crook, U.S. Army Transport, undated (Box 27, Folder 246)
    - Dixie, in New York Harbor, [1909] (Box 27, Folder 246)
    - Grant, U.S. Army Transport, undated (Box 27, Folder 247)
    - Illinois, undated (Box 27, Folder 247)
    - Kentucky, undated (Box 27, Folder 248)
    - Kilpatrick, U.S. Army Transport (3), [1900], 1908 (Box 27, Folder 248)
    - Logan, U.S. Army Transport, [1909] (Box 27, Folder 248)
    - U.S.S. Massachusetts(2), [1898] (Box 27, Folder 249)
    - Mauretania, Cunard Line, undated (Box 27, Folder 249)
    - McPherson, U.S. Army Transport, undated (Box 27, Folder 249)
    - U.S.S. Minneapolis, undated (Box 27, Folder 250)
    - U.S.S. Minnesota, [1898] (Box 27, Folder 250)
    - Minnesotan, undated (Box 27, Folder 250)
    - Missouri, U.S. Transport at Dows Docks, undated (Box 27, Folder 251)
    - Missouri?, warship, undated (Box 27, Folder 251)
    - Missouri, with west side of Manhattan, undated (Box 27, Folder 251)
    - U.S.S. New Orleans, undated (Box 28, Folder 252)
    - U.S.S. New York, cruiser, undated (Box 28, Folder 252)
    - Olympia, U.S. Army Transport (2), undated (Box 28, Folder 253)
    - U.S.S. Oregon, [1898] (Box 28, Folder 253)
    - Prizessin Victoria Louise, Montclair in background (2), undated (Box 28, Folder 254)
    - Roosevelt, yacht, with crew (2), undated (Box 28, Folder 254)
    - Sartoga, [1905] (Box 28, Folder 255)
    - Slocum, U.S. Transport Tug, undated (Box 28, Folder 255)
    - Thomas, undated (Box 28, Folder 255)
    - Unidentified ships (12), undated (Box 28, Folder 256-258)
  - Miscellaneous - Unmounted
    - Election banner for Theodore Roosevelt and Charles W. Fairbanks, [1904] (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - Election banner for William H. Taft and James S. Sherman, [1908] (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - Hardenbergh Patent lot 39 [photograph of map], undated (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - Interior of Photographic Studio, unidentified, undated (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - New York Arcade Railway [photographs of architectural renderings] (3), undated (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - Poor Richard Illustrated [photograph of illustrated "Lessons for the Young and Old on Industry, Temperance, Frugality &e. by Benjamin Franklin", undated (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - Real estate record of Lenox farm house [photograph of record published by Charles Macrae, 1874], undated (Box 29, Folder 259)
    - Wells Fargo Coach (2 mounted prints) (Box 29, Folder 269)
  - Unidentified
    - Unidentified Churches - Unmounted (2 interiors, 2 exteriors), undated (Box 29, Folder 260)
    - Unidentified Churches - Mounted (1 interior, 1 exterior), undated (Box 29, Folder 261)
    - Unidentified Interiors - Unmounted (2), undated (Box 29, Folder 262)
    - Unidentified Interiors - Mounted (2), undated (Box 29, Folder 263)
    - Unidentified Military Camp - Mounted (2), undated (Box 29, Folder 264)
    - Unidentified Residences - Unmounted (5), undated (Box 29, Folder 265)
    - Unidentified Residences - Mounted (8), undated (Box 29, Folder 266-267)
    - Unidentified Views - Mounted (2), undated (Box 29, Folder 268)
- Series V: Negatives
  Series V consists of about 275 glass negatives of varying size. Some of the negatives in this collection were formerly part of the Negative File (PR 045), and have that file's assigned negative numbers on their enclosures. Negatives are arranged by size and thereunder by negative numbers. Those Hall negatives without negative numbers are arranged by subject. The oversize glass negatives should not generally be consulted due to their extreme fragility; researchers should discuss particular needs with a curator before obtaining access. The majority of the oversize negatives in this series are represented by photographic prints in Series I. Where numbers are missing from the numbered negative sequence, negatives bearing these numbers were either determined to belong to other collections or are presumed to have been destroyed.
  - 5 x 7 to 6 1/2 x 8 1/2 inches
    - New York City
      - 111 Broadway, including Caldwell, Weston & Co. [stereograph], undated (Box 30)
      - Coney Island, Brooklyn, New York (18), [1901-1914] (Box 30)
      - Maiden Lane, showing campaign banner for McKinley and Hobart [copy negative from 1892 original], undated (Box 30)
      - New York Harbor View, [1901-1914] (Box 30)
    - Other
      - Hoptacong, Lackawanna Railroad ship, [1901-1914] (Box 30)
      - Unidentified park view, [1901-1914] (Box 30)
  - 10 x 12 inches
    - Connecticut - Hartford
      - Morgan Memorial, 1913 Jul. 11 (Box 31)
    - District of Columbia
      - Washington Monument, [1884-1914] (Box 31)
    - Massachusetts - Boston
      - Emmanuel Church, 15 Newberry Street, funeral of Dr. William R. Huntington (3), 1909 Jul. 28 (Box 31)
    - Missouri - St. Louis
      - Street view, undated (Box 31)
    - New York - Garden City
      - Rural View, undated (Box 31)
    - New York - Newburgh
      - Joined view of Newburgh waterfront, undated (Box 31)
    - New York - Brooklyn
      - Ludwig van Beethoven Statue, Prospect Park, undated (Box 31)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music, undated (Box 31)
      - Oceanic Hotel [copy negative], [1901-1914] (Box 31)
      - Memorial Presbyterian Church, 186 St. James Place, undated (Box 31)
      - Summerfield Methodist Episcopal Church, Greene and Washington Avenues, undated (Box 31)
      - George Washington Equestrian Statue, Washington Plaza, Williamsburg, [1901-1914] (Box 31)
    - New York - Manhattan
      - 14th Street Theatre, [1880-1910] (Box 31)
      - 69th Regiment Armory, 68 Lexington Avenue, interior and exterior (2), [1910], undated (Box 31)
      - 49-52 Broadway, [1911] (Box 31)
      - 212 Broadway, United Building, [1910] (Box 31)
      - Broadway and Fulton Street, subway fire, [1905] (Box 31)
      - Central Park (3), undated (Box 31)
      - City Hall Park [copy of 1903 original], undated (Box 31)
      - Flatiron Building [Fuller Building], [1902-1914] (Box 31)
      - Grace Church, 800 Broadway [copy of ca. 1883-1901 original], undated (Box 31)
      - George P. Hall &Son Studio interiors (3), [1883-1914] (Box 31)
      - Jewish Messenger, 70th Street and Central Park West, [1880-1902] (Box 32)
      - Lower Manhattan from New Jersey [copy], [1910] (Box 32)
      - Hotel Marlborough and Rathskeller, [1910] (Box 32)
      - Mohawk Apartment Hotel, 450 West 57th Street, undated (Box 32)
      - New York Harbor [copy of lithograph], undated (Box 32)
      - Park Row, from St. Paul's Chapel [copy of 1902 Hall photograph], undated (Box 32)
      - Putnam House, 271 Fourth Avenue, undated (Box 32)
      - Staats-Zeitung Building, undated (Box 32)
      - Statue of Liberty [copy of 1898 Hall photograph - positive], undated (Box 32)
      - Union Square, Lafayette statue, undated (Box 32)
    - New York - Queens
      - Flushing (3), undated (Box 32)
      - Queensborough Public Library Ridgewood Heights branch, undated (Box 32)
    - New York - Shelter Island (2), undated (Box 32)
    - New York - Yonkers (11), undated (Box 32)
    - Portraits
      - Ulysses S. Grant [copy negative of 4 cartes-de-visite], undated (Box 33)
      - George P. Hall, group photograph with three man labeled Jordan, Erving, and Norris, [1880-1900] (Box 33)
      - James S. Hall [copy negative], undated (Box 33)
      - Hall, unidentified females in the Hall family (2 items), undated (Box 33)
      - Henry Hudson [painting], undated (Box 33)
      - Las Dos Americas, portrait of staff in office interior, 1907 (Box 33)
      - Unidentified (7), undated (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Hudson County Democrat, Hoboken newspaper, partial page From Saturday, October 6, 1866 discussing Democratic Congressional Convention, undated (Box 33)
      - Letter of introduction for James S. Hall to N.C. Rogers, esq. from E. &H.T. Anthony &Co., [1890-1899] (Box 33)
      - Perry's Victory on Lake Erie, [painting], undated (Box 33)
    - Unidentified
      - Building exteriors (4), 1914, undated (Box 33)
      - Building interiors (6), [1900], undated (Box 33)
  - 11 x 14 to 11 x 18 inches
    - Alabama, undated (Box 34, Folder 61056)
    - Unidentified ship, undated (Box 34, Folder 61057)
    - U.S. Army Transport Buford, undated (Box 34, Folder 61058)
    - Thomas, undated (Box 34, Folder 61059)
    - Missouri, undated (Box 34, Folder 61060)
    - Unidentified ship, undated (Box 34, Folder 61061)
    - Transport Tug Slocum, undated (Box 34, Folder 61062)
    - Two tugs and Army Transport, undated (Box 34, Folder 61063)
    - Illinois, undated (Box 34, Folder 61064)
    - U.S. Army Transport Crook, undated (Box 34, Folder 61065)
    - Chicago, undated (Box 34, Folder 61066)
    - Unidentified Ship, undated (Box 35, Folder 61067)
    - U.S. Army Transport McPherson, undated (Box 35, Folder 61068)
    - Kentucky, undated (Box 35, Folder 61069)
    - Unidentified town view, undated (Box 35, Folder 61070)
    - Unidentified Bridge, undated (Box 35, Folder 61071)
    - Southern Manhattan, East River, undated (Box 35, Folder 61072)
    - U.S. Army Transport Kilpatrick, undated (Box 35, Folder 61073)
    - Manhattan Beach Hotel, [1905-1910] (Box 35, Folder 61074)
    - Broad Street, 1912 (Box 35, Folder 61075)
    - Whitehall Building, undated (Box 35, Folder 61076)
    - Battery Park, harbor view, undated (Box 35, Folder 61077)
    - Unidentified bridge, undated (Box 36, Folder 61078)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, 1903 (Box 36, Folder 61079)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, undated (Box 36, Folder 61081)
    - Leila M. Hall [Mrs. J.S. Hall], portrait, undated (Box 36, Folder 61082)
    - Unidentified residence, undated (Box 36, Folder 61083)
    - Soldiers and Sailors Monument, undated (Box 36, Folder 61084)
    - Olympia, U.S. Army Transport, undated (Box 36, Folder 61085)
    - Estherson's Family Wine and Liquor Store, undated (Box 36, Folder 61086)
    - Madison Avenue at 56th Street, undated (Box 36, Folder 61087)
    - Unidentified ship, undated (Box 36, Folder 61088)
    - Unidentified man [in early roadster, goggles on head], undated (Box 36, Folder 61089)
    - RMS Baltic, undated (Box 37, Folder 61090)
    - Warship Missouri, undated (Box 37, Folder 61091)
    - Prinzessin Victoria Louise, Montclair in background, undated (Box 37, Folder 61092)
    - St. Paul's Chapel, undated (Box 37, Folder 61093)
    - Unidentified U.S. Army Transport Ship, undated (Box 37, Folder 61094)
    - Manhattan Refrigerating Co., West Street, undated (Box 37, Folder 61095)
    - Manhattan Beach view, undated (Box 37, Folder 61096)
    - Unidentified military camp, undated (Box 37, Folder 61097)
    - Pennsylvania Station, excavation site, [1903] (Box 37, Folder 61098)
    - Broadway, 271, at Chambers Street, undated (Box 37, Folder 61099)
    - E.H. Van Ingen Co. Building[The Mohawk], undated (Box 37, Folder 61100)
    - Brooklyn Bridge and New York skyline, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 61101)
    - Brooklyn Bridge and East River views, undated (Box 38, Folder 61102-61104)
    - Unidentified residence, undated (Box 38, Folder 61105)
    - American Surety Building, 1898 (Box 38, Folder 61106)
    - Unidentified woman, undated (Box 38, Folder 61107)
    - Coney Island, undated (Box 38, Folder 61108)
    - Oriental Hotel, Manhattan Beach, [1905-1910] (Box 38, Folder 61109)
    - Manhattan Beach, undated (Box 38, Folder 61110)
    - Campaign Banner for Seth Low, [1901] (Box 39, Folder 61111)
    - Wall Street, undated (Box 39, Folder 61112)
    - Singer Building, undated (Box 39, Folder 61113)
    - Graduation ceremony, unidentified, undated (Box 39, Folder 61114)
    - Montauk, undated (Box 39, Folder 61115)
    - Unidentified military camp, undated (Box 39, Folder 61116)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences [Brooklyn Museum], 1912 (Box 39, Folder 61117)
    - Unidentified buildings, undated (Box 40, Folder 61118-61122)
    - Brighton Beach, bathing pavilion, undated (Box 40, Folder 61123)
    - Unidentified buildings, undated (Box 40, Folder 61124-61125)
    - Fire department building, 367-369 Jay Street, near Myrtle Avenue, undated (Box 40, Folder 61127)
    - Sagtikos Manor, West Bay Shore, Long Island, undated (Box 40, Folder 61128-61131)
    - Sagtikos Manor, [1902] (Box 41, Folder 61132)
    - Jamaica Avenue, near Long Island Railroad crossing, undated (Box 41, Folder 61133)
    - Unidentified parade, undated (Box 41, Folder 61134)
    - Sagtikos Manor, interiors, [1902] (Box 41, Folder 61135-61137)
    - Unidentified waterfront view (9 x 11"), undated (Box 41, Folder 61138)
    - Bowling Green, undated (Box 42, Folder 61139)
    - Construction scene, unidentified building, undated (Box 42, Folder 61140)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, undated (Box 42, Folder 61141)
    - New York Harbor, undated (Box 42, Folder 61142)
    - City Hall Park, [1903] (Box 42, Folder 61143)
    - Grand Central Terminal, looking north from 41st Street, [1896] (Box 43, Folder 66600)
    - Fifth Avenue, looking north above 53rd Street, east side, undated (Box 43, Folder 66601)
    - [Bird's Eye view of lower Manhattan, copy of a painting by Moses King, ca. 1903], undated (Box 43, Folder 66602)
    - Holy Trinity Church, 42nd Street &Madison Avenue [Dr. Tyng's Church], 1880 (Box 43, Folder 66604)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, Manhattan Tower, 1898 (Box 43, Folder 66605)
    - Cooper Square, [1909] (Box 43, Folder 66606)
    - Herald Square, 33rd Street, Broadway and Fifth Avenue, undated (Box 43, Folder 66607)
    - Central Park South, undated (Box 43, Folder 66608)
    - Fifth Avenue Building, Fifth Avenue and 23rd Street, 1909 (Box 43, Folder 66609)
    - St. Paul's Chapel, undated (Box 43, Folder 66610)
    - Hanover Square, Elevated trains winding between buildings, undated (Box 43, Folder 66611)
    - U.S.S. Indiana, undated (Box 43, Folder 66612)
    - Fifth Avenue and 51st Street, Vanderbilt Houses, undated (Box 43, Folder 66613)
    - Park Row and Frankfort Street, "Homeward Bound", 1906 (Box 43, Folder 66614)
    - Cavalry charge of Lt. Henry B. Hidden [copy of painting by V. Nehlig, 1862], undated (Box 43, Folder 66615)
    - Unidentified church interior, undated (Box 43, Folder 66633)
    - Unidentified church interior, undated (Box 43, Folder 66635)
    - Unidentified parade, undated (Box 43, Folder 66636)
    - Trinity Church, undated (Box 43, Folder 66637)
    - Wall Street [copy of 1864 photograph], undated (Box 43, Folder 66638)
    - The New-York Historical Society, exterior, [1908-1912] (Box 43, Folder 66644-66646)
    - Liberty Street, Singer Building in background, undated (Box 44, Folder 66647)
    - Manhattan Life Insurance Building, with Trinity Church, undated (Box 44, Folder 66648)
    - Broad Street, New York Stock Exchange, 1904 (Box 44, Folder 66649)
    - Unidentified view, undated (Box 44, Folder 66650)
    - Sloane Maternity Hospital, 447 West 59th Street, undated (Box 44, Folder 66651)
  - 11 x 18 inches (broken)
    - Manhattan - Cathedral of St. John the Divine [Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine], 1898 (Box 45)
    - Manhattan - Maiden Lane, 87-89, [1895-1905] (Box 45)
    - Manhattan - Park Row, rooftop view, undated (Box 45)
    - University Club, 1 West 54th Street, [1900-1914] (Box 45)
  - 14 x 17 inches
    - Brooklyn
      - Coney Island street views (5), undated (Box 46)
    - Governor's Island, undated (Box 46)
    - Manhattan
      - Bellevue Hospital, 1909 (Box 46)
      - Finanacial District, rooftop view, [1905] (Box 46)
      - Ulysses S. Grant's Funeral, Fifth Avenue and 33rd Street [copy negative of 1885 original], undated (Box 46)
      - Hudson Terminal, City Investing, and Singer Building, 1908 (Box 46)
      - Knickerbocker HOtel, undated (Box 46)
      - Knickerbocker Trust Co., undated (Box 46)
      - Manhattan Bridge, undated (Box 46)
      - New York Public Library, undated (Box 46)
      - New York skyline panorama (3), undated (Box 47)
      - New York skyline, ships in foreground, undated (Box 47)
      - St. Paul's Church, undated (Box 47)
      - Trinity Church (3), undated (Box 47)
      - Washington Square Park, rooftop view from southwest, [1892-1914] (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Bank of Cuba, undated (Box 47)
      - Priscilla[ship], undated (Box 47)
      - Group portrait of six men, one holding a stereograph camera, undated (Box 47)
      - Southern Railroad, Lynchburg, Virginia (2 parts of panorama), undated (Box 47)
  - 17 x 20 inches
    - Haverley's Theatre, Brooklyn, undated (Box 48)
    - Sans Souci Hotel, Ballston Spa, New York, undated (Box 48)
    - New York view from water, including Pier 21, undated (Box 48)
    - Unidentified Mansion, undated (Box 48)
    - Unidentified buildings (3), undated (Box 49)
    - Unidentified view, undated (Box 49)
  - 18 x 22 inches
    - Manhattan
      - City Hall and City Hall Park, rooftop view, undated (Box 50)
      - Consolidated Exchange, O.D. Budd &Co., undated (Box 50)
      - East River, from Brooklyn toward Manhattan, undated (Box 50)
      - Hamburg American Building, rooftop view, undated (Box 50)
      - Mail &Express Building, undated (Box 50)
      - Royal Insurance Building, rooftop view, undated (Box 50)
    - Unidentified
      - Unidentified demolition scene, undated (Box 50)
      - Unidentified building, undated (Box 51)
      - Unidentified churches (3), undated (Box 51)
      - Unidentified group portrait of men in front of building, undated (Box 51)
      - Unidentified library interior, undated (Box 51)
      - Unidentified view [rural], undated (Box 51)
      - Unidentified Bridge [broken, now 14 x 22 inches], undated (Box 52)
    - Copy negatives
      - New York Stock Exchange [copy negative of 1881 original by Beal], undated (Box 52)
      - Trinity Church [copy negative of lithograph], undated (Box 52)
      - Seventh Regiment Parade [copy negative], undated (Box 52)
  - Various oversize (2010 Donation)
    - Penn Station excavation, undated (Box 53)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, undated (Box 54)
    - Lusitania [broken, loss at corner], undated (Box 55)
    - City Hall, undated (Box 56)
      Existence and Location of Copies note
      A transparency of this image is located in Box 29, Folder 269.
    - Orient Hotel, Coney Island (Box 57)
    - Bowery [looking N.], undated (Box 58)
      A transparency of this image is located in Box 29, Folder 269
    - Mt. Pelee, Coney Island, undated (Box 59)
    - 145th Street and Broadway, undated (Box 60)
    - Atlantic Avenue and Bedford Avenue, undated (Box 61)
    - NYC skyline from water, undated (Box 62)
    - Columbus Circle, undated (Box 63)
    - Herald Square, undated (Box 64)
    - Montauk, undated (Box 65)
    - Fulton Street (or Barclay Street?), undated (Box 66)
    - Madison Square, undated (Box 67)
    - Long Island City (Prospect St. and St. Jane St.), undated (Box 68)
    - Saratoga [ship], undated (Box 69)
    - Niagara Falls (2), undated (Box 69)
    - Niagara Falls (4), undated (Box 70)
    - Niagara Falls, undated (Box 71)
    - Ship in Hudson (“Slope”? – note written on box), undated (Box 72)
    - U.S. Army transport McClellen in NY Harbor, undated (Box 72)
    - U.S. Sedgwick in NY Harbor [cracked] (Box 72)
    - Copy negative of painting – portrait of Henry Drissler, undated (Box 73)
    - Copy negative of painting – portrait of F.A.P. Barnard, undated (Box 73)
    - Copy negative of painting – portrait of Samuel Johnson, undated (Box 73)
    - Copy negative of historical botanical diagram (?), undated (Box 73)
    - Copy negative of historical letter signed by John Van Cortland et al., undated (Box 73)
    - Copy negative of painting, undated (Box 73)
    - Third Avenue Railway - Fort Lee Ferry street car– Riverside Drive (?), undated (Box 74)
    - Sir Thomas Lipton on boat deck, undated (Box 74)
    - Unidentified man, seated in uniform (Salvation Army?), undated (Box 74)
    - Open drawbridge, undated (Box 74)
    - University Club (?) (54th and Fifth Ave.), undated (Box 74)
    - Brooklyn Bridge and docks, from Manhattan, undated (Box 75)
- Series VI: Logbooks